publisherrev.com 2016-10-18

# PublisherRev : Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

**Incite Network LLC's PublisherRev.com Privacy Policy**

Last updated September 3, 2008.

PLEASE NOTE: OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME AND CHANGES ARE EFFECTIVE UPON POSTING. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES AS IT IS YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AWARE OF CHANGES. INCITE NETWORK LLC DOES NOT PROVIDE NOTICES OF CHANGES IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN BY POSTING THE CHANGES AT THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO INCITE NETWORK LLC OR USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEB SITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY.

The information collection, use, and dissemination practices of Incite Network LLC. This policy applies to Incite Network LLC's collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by Incite Network LLC on its (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries and related companies (collectively, the "Websites"), (b) on various third party websites, and (c) to Incite Network LLC's other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from third parties. Incite Network LLC is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third web sites or applications.

1\. Collection of Information.  
1.1 Survey Information.  
Incite Network LLC collects information from individuals by various methods, including, but not limited to, when an individual voluntarily completes an Incite Network LLC survey, order form, or a registration page either online or offline, or by means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties (collectively, a "Survey"). (As used herein, "online" means using the Internet, including the Websites, and related technologies, and "offline" means by methods other than online, including in person, in the postal mail, using telephones and cell phones, and other similar means.) In the Surveys, Incite Network LLC or a third party (a "Third Party") may ask an individual to provide various information to Incite Network LLC, which may include his or her name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, social security number, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time (together, "Survey Information"). Incite Network LLC may also collect information concerning an individual from another source and uses that information in combination with information provided from this web site. Completing the Surveys is completely voluntary, and individuals are under no obligation to provide Survey Information to Incite Network LLC or Third Party, but an individual may receive incentives from Incite Network LLC or a Third Party in exchange for providing Survey Information to Incite Network LLC.

1.2 Third Party List Information.  
Incite Network LLC collects information from individuals when an individual provides information to a third party and Incite Network LLC subsequently purchases, licenses, or otherwise acquires the information from the third party (the "Seller"). Such purchased information may include, but is not limited to, an individual's name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, industry of employment, personal and online interests, and such other information as the individual may have provided to the Seller (together, "Third Party List Information"). When acquiring Third Party List Information, Incite Network LLC seeks assurances from the Seller that the Seller has a right to transfer the Third Party List Information to Incite Network LLC and that the Seller has a right to provide offers from advertisers to the individuals whose personal information is included on the Seller's list.

1.3 Other Information.  
Other occasions when Incite Network LLC obtains information from individuals include (1) when an individual is making a claim for a prize or seeking to redeem an incentive offered by Incite Network LLC or by a third party, (2) when an individual requests assistance through Incite Network LLC's customer service department, and (3) when an individual voluntarily subscribes to a Incite Network LLC service or newsletter (together, "Other Information").

1.4 Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Info Collected Using Technology.  
Incite Network LLC currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about an individual with information about the individual in our database. Additionally, Incite Network LLC may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future (together, "Technology Information").  
(a) Cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of the individual's computer that allows Incite Network LLC to identify the individual with his or her corresponding data that resides in Incite Network LLC's database. You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com. Individuals who use the Websites need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the Websites.  
(b) Web Beacons. A web beacon is programming code that can be used to display an image on a web page (by using an img src="x" programming function -- see http://truste.org for more information), but can also be used to transfer an individual's unique user identification (often in the form of a cookie) to a database and associate the individual with previously acquired information about an individual in a database. This allows Incite Network LLC to track certain web sites an individual visits online. Web beacons are used to determine products or services an individual may be interested in, and to track online behavioral habits for marketing purposes. For example, Incite Network LLC might place, with the consent of a third party website, a web beacon on the third party's website where fishing products are sold. When Joe, an individual listed in Incite Network LLC's database, visits the fishing website, Incite Network LLC receives notice by means of the web beacon that Joe visited the fishing site, and Incite Network LLC would then update Joe's profile with the information that Joe is interested in fishing. Incite Network LLC may thereafter present offers of fishing related products and services to Joe. In addition to using web beacons on web pages, Incite Network LLC also uses web beacons in email messages sent to individuals listed in Incite Network LLC's database.  
(c) New Technology.  
The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly evolving, as is Incite Network LLC's use of new and evolving technology. As a result, Incite Network LLC strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of technology.

1.5 Outside Information.  
Incite Network LLC may receive information about individuals from third parties or from other sources of information outside of Incite Network LLC including information located in public databases ("Outside Information").

1.6 Individual Information.  
As used herein, Individual Information means Survey Information, Third Party List Information, Other Information, Technology Information, and Outside Information, and any other information Incite Network LLC gathers or receives about individuals.

1.7 No Information Collected from Children.  
Incite Network LLC will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If Incite Network LLC obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because it does not collect such information, Incite Network LLC has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. Incite Network LLC has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

1.8 Credit Card Information.  
Incite Network LLC may in certain cases collect credit card numbers and related information, such as the expiration date of the card ("Credit Card Information") when an individual places an order from Incite Network LLC. When the Credit Card Information is submitted to Incite Network LLC, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. Incite Network LLC will use the Credit Card Information for purposes of processing and completing the purchase transaction, and the Credit Card Information will be disclosed to third parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction.

2\. Use of Individual Information.  
2.1 Discretion to Use Information.

The following paragraphs in Section 2 describe how Incite Network LLC currently uses Individual Information, but Incite Network LLC may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted below, Incite Network LLC may update this policy from time to time. Incite Network LLC may use Individual Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses.

2.2 Email. Incite Network LLC uses Individual Information to provide promotional offers by email to individuals. Incite Network LLC may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If email recipients wish to end their email subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe from the particular list. To unsubscribe from all Incite Network LLC's email lists, a person must send an email to support@publisherrev.com.  
2.2(a) Content of Email Messages.  
In certain commercial email messages sent by Incite Network LLC, an advertiser's name will appear in the "From:" line but hitting the "Reply" button will cause a reply email to be sent to Incite Network LLC. The "Subject:" line of Incite Network LLC email messages will usually contain a line provided from the advertiser to Incite Network LLC  
2.2(b) Solicited Email.  
Incite Network LLC only sends email to individuals who have agreed on the Websites to receive email from Incite Network LLC or to individuals who have agreed on third party websites to receive email from third parties such as Incite Network LLC. Incite Network LLC does not send unsolicited email messages. As a result, statutes requiring certain formatting for unsolicited email are not applicable to Incite Network LLC's email messages.  
2.3 Targeted Advertising.  
Incite Network LLC uses Individual Information to target advertising to an individual. When an individual is using the Internet, Incite Network LLC uses Technology Information (see also Section 2.5 below) to associate an individual with that person's Individual Information, and Incite Network LLC attempts to show advertising for products and services in which the person has expressed an interest in the Surveys, indicated an interest by means of Technology Information, and otherwise. Incite Network LLC may, at its discretion, target advertising by using email, direct mail, telephones, cell phones, and other means of communication to provide promotional offers.

2.4 Direct Mail and Telemarketing.  
Incite Network LLC uses Individual Information to advertise, directly or indirectly, to individuals using direct mail marketing or telemarketing using telephones and cell phones.  
2.5 Use of Technology Information.  
Incite Network LLC uses Technology Information (1) to match a person's Survey Information and Third Party List Information to other categories of Individual Information to make and improve profiles of individuals, (2) to track a person's online browsing habits on the Internet, (3) to determine which areas of Incite Network LLC's web sites are most frequently visited. This information helps Incite Network LLC to better understand the online habits of individuals so that Incite Network LLC can target advertising and promotions to them.  
2.6 Profiles of Individuals.  
Incite Network LLC uses Individual Information to make a profile of an individual. A profile can be created by combining Survey Information and Third Party List Information with other sources of Individual Information such as information obtained from public databases.  
2.7 Storage of Individual Information.  
Incite Network LLC stores the Individual Information in a database on Incite Network LLC computers. Our computers have security measures (such as a firewall) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under Incite Network LLC's control. Not withstanding such measures, Incite Network LLC cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent Incite Network LLC computers from being illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered.

3\. Dissemination of Individual Information.  
3.1 Sale or Transfer to Third Parties.  
Incite Network LLC WILL NOT SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY PURPOSE.  
3.2 Order Fulfillment.  
Incite Network LLC will transfer Individual Information to third parties when necessary to provide a product or service that a person orders from such third party while using Incite Network LLC web sites or when responding to offers provided by Incite Network LLC.  
3.3 Legal Process.  
Incite Network LLC may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and other legal processes.  
3.4 Summary Data.  
Incite Network LLC may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about all persons or sub-groups of persons.  
3.5 Access.  
Individuals have access to their Individual Information collected to provide an opportunity for an individual to correct, amend, or delete such information. Access can be obtained by contacting support@publisherrev.com. Incite Network LLC may also grant advertising clients and email services providers' access to an individual's email address to verify the origin of the Individual Information collected.

4\. Privacy Practices of Third Parties.  
4.1 Advertiser cookies and web beacons.  
Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (together, "Advertisers") who place advertisements on the Websites and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Incite Network LLC does not control Advertisers' use of such technology and Incite Network LLC has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals.  
4.2 Links.  
The Websites and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the web sites of third parties. Incite Network LLC is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites. Linked web sites may contain links to web sites maintained by third parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. Incite Network LLC does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such third party web sites. The inclusion of a link to a web site does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization.  
4.3 Affiliated Companies.  
Incite Network LLC may disclose, transfer, and sell Individual Information to entities affiliated with Incite Network LLC in Incite Network LLC's discretion.

If you have any questions on this privacy policy, please contact us at [support@publisherrev.com](mailto:support@publisherrev.com).
